Jhala
Ajay,
friends, how have we set up a modern toe,
in which
we have set up for the plateau, the name of the stock
is ICICI Lombard. Okay, now the reason behind
why we have selected this stock is
that the market came out on the
20th, a carpenter chapter note,
and from here we are closing, finally there was
a support here and yes, a bank came into the complex, from
here the price gave a good moment, it moved up
again, and
after moving up, I
went above the update level and again a falling down
examination form appeared from here, so
what is the logic of taking the spread easily, that there is a
little protection in it,
you must be able to understand, you must be seeing a
double bottom of the form
or pattern here, I am going to
discuss everything,
in the upcoming video I am going to go to Jhansi,
you will get a video about the project, so you will see that the
quantum is done and the same again,
another item is clicking here  So
behind the straight, we are going to talk mostly from here
and behind it our Ghaghra
market should open somewhere in this range and
consolidate a bit, after that we will
breakfast Stan, it will unite on this channel,
so the candle which will report to this channel,
do our show on the same channel and
then we will have another one on the straight line, we will
take a plate here, this will be our target
and if this level on this tomato
breaks again, then if our
channel of moment gets fragmented from here,
you will see it with
because this egg heavy support was added, when it
came here for the first time, it was
seen in Brahma from here, but it continued, then it came
half an inch from here,
but it does not break this level
and this mark, then I will
not tell you because behind it there is
more ghee support level below it, many times there was
a good business in it, so we
will gift bikes to this stock, spaceships, if Sanam
refers to it, we will do the next experiment and the one who
breaks it, his release will be
our Star Plus, friends, let's
meet you next time.  In the video